Hello, Bashar.
>> And to you, good day.
>> Yes,
since I was a little kid, I always have
been excited about
>> Speak up so that others may hear you.
>> I've always been excited about
spaceships, getting a spacecraft one
day.
>> Getting a spacecraft one day. [laughter]
>> travel in the in the intergalactic and
be a part of the other worlds.
>> So,
>> First,
the steps toward that, as you know, is
to follow the formula while your feet
are on the ground.
>> Yeah.
>> And if that is something relevant for
your life, then the opportunities and
circumstances will arrange themselves to
allow that to manifest.
>> Yes. So,
yeah, right now I'm in science and
technology. So, uh we're working on
anti-gravity, but I
I believe there is a easier way to
>> Well, there is. Because anti-gravity is
not actually anti-gravity.
It has nothing to do with being
anti-gravity.
It has to do with relocation of the
locational variable
within every object.
>> Okay.
>> Do you understand that explanation?
>> Mhm.
>> Was that a no?
>> Um not really.
>> Then say, "No, I don't understand it."
>> No, I don't understand it.
>> Thank you for your honesty.
This is how it works, and this is how
our craft work in going from star to
star.
Many people on your planet consider an
object to be in a location.
>> Mhm.
>> Yes? So, you have an object. No matter
what it is, let's say it's a cup. And
it's in this location. And now you take
this cup and you move it to this
location. You people think it's the same
cup.
It's not.
Because the cup in this location
has a different locational variable in
its energy signature. Location is a part
of the object.
It's not a place the object exists in.
Therefore, when you move the cup, what
you're doing is you're actually changing
its locational variable all along the
way so that it goes from here to here,
but it's not the same cup really because
it contains a slightly different
locational variable in its overall
energy equation.
So, I have just given you a lateral
definition, but that still also works
this way. Vertically, too. So, if you
have something that's on the ground, it
has a specific location. If you take
that object and put it up here in the
air, it has a different location.
Different variable in its equation. So,
if you can map the difference
between the two vibrationally, if you
have instruments that are sensitive
enough to be able to read the entire
energy frequency location variable here
and the entire collective signature
vibration of the object here, then when
you put the object on the ground, you
can shall we say bombard it whether
electronically or acoustically or it
really doesn't matter how, magnetically,
but you bombard it with the vibration
that contains the locational variable of
up here.
And then if you have enough energy going
on to it, you can overwhelm in a sense
and replace its locational variable on
the ground and it will suddenly have to
go to the location that is represented
by the new variable you are imposing on
it.
That's, quote and quote, anti-gravity.
It doesn't mean there is no gravity, it
just means you have redefined its
locational variable within the
gravitational field.
That's how it works. And that's how we
go from star to star.
We know the locational variable, let's
say, of your solar system and how
different it is from our solar system in
our dimension.
So, we isolate our craft with a type of
energy bubble that sort of neutralizes
it from any particular reality, and then
we impose within the craft a vibration
of the location we wish to go to. The
craft has to stop existing at the first
location and automatically and
immediately start existing at the second
location, ideally with the crew inside.
>> [laughter]
>> Because it's all wrapped in that
vibrational bubble. We haven't traveled,
really, the intervening distance. We
have simply redefined where we are in
another here and now, another version of
here and now. In some ways, it might
actually be more accurate to say that we
haven't gone to the new location, we
have recreated the location where we
are.
>> Mhm.
>> But because you see it from a space-time
perspective, it looks like we have gone
from there to here.
Does that help?
>> Yeah, but then you don't actually need a
spaceship, you can just teleport
yourself, then.
>> Yes, we understand, and that is possible
as well, and that we all do that anyway,
because even when you're walking across
a room, you're teleporting yourself.
It's just that you're doing it in such
small steps, you don't think you're
doing it. That's the point. But the main
reason we have ships is because the
ships also represent a symbiotic
relationship with our higher minds in a
crystalline form, in a physical form,
and also many of the civilizations that
we make first contact with need to
understand us in a way they can
understand us, and for many
civilizations, it's easier for them to
absorb contact with another civilization
when they come in a ship
than somebody who just suddenly appears
behind them and and goes boo.
>> [laughter]
>> It would, as you say, freak them out too
much. So, often times, the idea of our
ships are maintained for your benefit
rather than ours.
Does that help?
>> Yes.
>> So, the experiment, as we have defined
it before, is to take a very long, flat
table, as perfectly flat as you can make
it, and have it be at least 10 ft long.
Take a hollow sphere of some material
that you can resonate, such as copper or
steel or what have you, as thin a shell
as you can make it, but still make it as
perfectly round as you can make it, and
hollow, so it's light and there's not a
lot of material there.
And take a measurement, get it
vibrating, and take a measurement
somehow of what the entire signature
frequency is. Then, literally physically
move it to the other end of the table,
take another measurement. Put it back at
the beginning, and then bombard it with
the energy, overwhelming the material
with the energy of the second frequency,
however you wish to do that. As I said,
magnetically, electronically,
acoustically, and watch the ball roll to
the other location and stop.
That's how you test this principle. And
then, you can start mapping from
whatever you consider to be point zero,
what the different locational variables
are in a matrix map out as far as you
want to go. And then, you'll be able to
calculate exactly what formula of
frequency to impose upon your ship to go
to that specific location when you get
far enough along in understanding this
technology. Does that help?
>> Uh somehow. Uh
you have to understand the technology,
of course.
>> Well, you have to take baby steps.
Because
there are things that can happen
even in our civilization, when we first
really started experimenting with this,
we had situations and circumstances
where the ship wound where it needed to
go, but the crew did not.
>> Okay.
>> We have told this story before and we
have used it in a positive way because
from our perspective the idea is is that
crew in a sense
disappeared and they were spread
throughout creation.
So, now we know that no matter where we
go, there is always a part of us waiting
there to greet us.
That's the purpose
that that crew served for the rest.
So, but take the baby steps. There's a
lot to learn. Your technology is not
quite at the point where you can be
refined enough to really read those
specific locational variables as clearly
as you need to. So, you need to improve
the technology even of being able to
even read those signature frequencies to
be able to tell the difference between
those two locations. You have to isolate
that locational variable. You're not
even there yet.
So, take the time. It's fun.
>> Yeah.
>> Learn it. Really become a master of it.
That's what's fun about it.
>> Step by step.
So, okay. I have another question. Um
yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Uh
I um
always see a lot of
geometric patterns and um
>> So, um
It's It's good to good to look at. It's
It's fantastic, but uh I believe that
there's a language there. But
>> Well, there is.
>> So, how can I translate it?
>> in fact, that actually might be able to
help you read the locational variable
more easily because if you can see those
patterns, you might be able to interpret
those frequencies in a geometric way.
That's how we do it that actually makes
more sense to you and is easier for you
to be able to see the variable you need
to see. So, you can use it that way. You
can apply it that way.
>> Yeah.
>> So, that might be part of your ability
to learn to do this.
>> Yeah, that's the thing. So, how do I I
read it?
>> You'll figure that out. When you start
taking the vibrational readings, look
and see what kind of patterns you're
seeing and look at the difference in the
patterns between the two locations.
Learn the language and learn how to read
the language by doing the experiment we
gave you and seeing how the patterns
might be different.
>> Yeah.
>> That's one way you can use it. Use your
imagination.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> I try to do that.
>> Well, just do it. Don't try, just do it.
>> Yeah, and sometimes I just
go
I see I can see my DNA structure. So,
it's like you're tapping into your own
control room and it's like now I can
actually program or reprogram, but it's
like I don't I don't know how to do it.
>> But you will.
But this is part of the process.
You need to go through the process so
that you can really make it your own so
that you can really understand it and
really master it. You can't just be
given the end result. You won't know
what to do with it. You won't even
understand it until you have learned
your way of relating to it, your way of
understanding it.
When people go into in your planet
physics classes, they are not given the
end result most difficult cutting edge
formulas and equations. They have to
learn from the scratch and the get-go
and the building what that all means so
they can become familiar with all the
symbols and all the meanings and then
it's a richer experience and then you
can diversify and go off because you
already know the so-called rules and you
now know how to bend them.
You have to learn them first before you
can bend them.
>> So, I create my way.
>> Of course. Your way will be the way that
you understand. You can't do it any
other way. You have to do it your way,
but you have to learn what your way is
as part of the process.
>> So, that's actually the That's what's
holding me back because
>> Yes.
>> I am trying to understand
>> things that are too advanced for you to
understand right now.
>> It's like a template or manual, but it
isn't. I I I have to create create
create a new
>> to create your own template, yeah.
>> Yeah.
Okay.
>> So, have fun.
>> Thank you very much.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> [applause]
>> REMEMBER,
ALL OF THE GREAT breakthroughs in your
society were created by people who
allowed themselves to think outside the
box once they understood what the box
was.
So, you need to understand the box, then
you know how to think outside of it.
>> Hi, Bashar.
>> Have a new you good day.
>> Okay, I have three questions for you.
>> Yes.
>> Uh first one is uh the recent disasters,
earthquakes, and hurricane.
>> Exciting, isn't it?
>> Does it relates to uh solar eclipse?
>> Well, in a sense, yes, because it's
certainly the result of choices and
consequences that people are making
in terms of their relationship to nature
in which some people in your society
believe certain things and some people
believe different things.
There's a lot of denial within
fear-based beliefs about what's
connecting to what and a refusal to see
your planet as an entire system.
Well, then making certain choices from
that refusal to understand your planet
as an entire system will allow certain
things to occur that may not necessarily
be exactly as pleasant as you would
prefer them to be.
But, if people are going to from one
level decide that they're going to wake
up, but they're not willing to do it in
a smooth way by understanding the
system, then they're going to do things
to shock themselves awake. They're going
to do things to force themselves to pay
attention to what's going on in terms of
the consequences of the choices you're
making for the planet.
>> So, we choose it.
We choose
>> you do.
Do you understand that
what you call weather is a reflection of
the collective emotional state of your
entire mass consensus?
>> Yes, I can understand that.
>> Well, there you go.
>> Okay, my second question is I've always
had dream about uh doing a genetic
engineering.
>> Yes.
>> And uh is this a something I do
past or I'm doing it right now?
>> You are making connections to what might
be colloquially called past lives,
particularly in Atlantis where a lot of
genetic engineering was done.
>> Yes.
>> But now that it's coming back into your
society as a technology,
there are other ways for you to use this
unless you are actually interested in
expressing it specifically that way.
>> I just feel guilty about it for some
reason.
>> You don't need to.
You really don't. You have learned your
lessons by making those connections and
you understand now that it is to your
benefit to use whatever information you
are gleaning from this in positive and
constructive ways instead of destructive
ones, don't you?
>> Well, there was a dream that I you know,
I created the this animal, but it didn't
have
>> you.
Because you don't have another life not
as you. On the higher level, yes, but
again, the point is did you learn
something from it? Like, for example,
not doing it again.
>> Yes.
>> Then you have erased the negativity in
the connection by learning the lesson.
So, there's nothing to feel guilty
about.
>> There's tendency though.
>> There's not tendency. There is only
choice.
Tendency is nothing else but to choose
to believe that you don't have a choice.
When people say tendency, it's a denial
of the fact that they're choosing. They
just may be unaware of the fact that
they're choosing, so they say, "Oh, I
have a tendency." No, you don't. You're
making a choice. It may just be an
unconscious one, which is again why it's
so important to get in conscious contact
with the definitions that you are
choosing to believe in.
Tendency is just another way of saying
I'm making an unconscious choice.
So, get in touch with it. And it won't
be a tendency, it'll be a choice.
>> Okay.
So, I should explore that
>> You can.
I'm not saying you should, because we
never say you should, but I'm saying you
could.
>> Okay, and my third question um
is is hypnosis is a
bad thing?
>> Is what?
>> Hypnosis.
>> Depends on how you use it, isn't it?
Isn't everything capable of being used
in a positive or a negative way?
>> Yes.
>> Well, a positive way is to understand
that hypnosis can be used to unlock you
from
other definitions that don't work for
you.
>> Well, of course I have the, you know,
positive intent, you know, intent of it,
but like
>> But what? If you have a positive intent,
why would you assume that you would use
it in a negative way?
>> Because it feels like unnatural.
>> It feels unnatural?
>> Yes.
>> Do you understand that your entire
physical reality is unnatural? You're
creating it from your consciousness. It
doesn't exist on its own.
>> But it's like I'm like intervening
someone's life.
>> Are they there willingly asking you to
do it, or are you forcing it on them?
Then how are you intervening in a way
that they haven't asked you to?
>> Okay.
>> Do you understand?
>> Yes.
>> Does that help?
>> There you go.
>> Thank you.
>> I have now hypnotized you into
understanding this.
>> [applause]
>> Hi Bashar.
>> And a you good day.
>> Um, okay. So, I have a question about
synchronicity.
>> Yes.
>> In the past couple of months I've
experienced insane amount of
synchronicity.
>> Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> We experience it every moment of every
day.
>> So lucky.
Um
>> So were you.
>> Thank you.
>> You're always experiencing it, remember?
Always. There is never a moment when
you're not experiencing synchronicity.
It's just that there is positive and
negative synchronicity.
>> So, I noticed that the more that I
experience synchronicity and the more
that I started realizing like
experiencing kind of the miraculous and
like wow, the power of moments and how
things can
>> Synchronicity is physical reality's
space-time way of demonstrating that
everything is connected, that everything
is one thing. It just has to do it in a
synchronous way because you are seeing
it through space and time. That's all.
>> That's exactly actually the lesson I
guess I've been learning from. But at
the same time what I've noticed is
>> Was that a joke?
>> It No.
>> At the same time?
>> Oh no. No, not at all.
But simultaneously
I
>> There's that joke again.
>> I've noticed that the more that I
experience such a high level of
synchronicity and and crazy moments, I
also experience a high degree of pain.
>> Oh, really? All right.
>> In what sense?
>> I'd say a lot of it is guilt.
>> About what?
Specifically about what?
>> Um
>> Why is experiencing
synchronicity allowing you to also
experience guilt?
>> Because I feel like the more that things
go well for me, I'm losing A, more of a
sense of myself, or B, it negatively
affects others.
>> Now, why are you holding on to those
beliefs that obviously, if you examine
them more closely, make no sense at all?
Because the more you experience
synchronicity, the more you actually are
being yourself. And by being yourself,
the more you are helping others by being
an example of someone being themselves.
So, in that light, what you're talking
about experiencing makes no sense. You
have contradictory definitions of things
that don't match the experience of
synchronicity.
>> But it almost feels like the more I'm
myself, sometimes I feel like
>> I understand what you're saying, but
you're not paying attention to the way
you're saying it. I understand you feel
that, but remember what we said? You
can't have a feeling without a
definition first.
>> Mhm.
>> Do you understand?
>> You can't feel anything if you don't
know what the definition of that thing
is. You won't know how to feel. So, the
fact that you might feel that more
strongly is your first clue that that
means it's putting you in touch with the
fact you have a definition that's out of
alignment with who you actually are. You
need to find out what that definition is
and let it appear nonsensical.
Cuz it doesn't make sense. It's not a
definition of being yourself.
To say that experiencing more
synchronicity gives me more pain because
somehow I'm doing some damage to someone
else, that makes no sense if you
understand what synchronicity is.
>> Okay, then part of Okay, then I want to
focus on just the idea of the pain part.
>> Yes.
>> A lot of it has to plays in part with
what I call emotional abuse.
>> Yes.
>> How I don't really have a question per
se, but how does how do you
>> was emotionally abused?
>> Me.
>> Really?
Are you sure?
>> Well, I feel
>> Are you the person now
who is being emotionally abused?
Now?
>> No.
>> Yes, you are.
Because you're doing it to yourself.
Because you've learned to do it to
yourself. That's what you were taught.
And so in a sense, you're perpetuating
the emotional abuse because you've been
trained to do so.
You don't have to.
Because now you understand that that's
not what you prefer.
You just don't understand that you're
the one now doing it to yourself.
Because you're so familiar with how to
do it.
Because you were taught how to do it.
Yes?
>> Yeah.
>> But you are not being emotionally abused
by anyone else
because you're too busy emotionally
abusing yourself.
No one else could do a better job at
this point other than you because you
know yourself best. So you know where
your buttons are. You know how to make
yourself feel bad and feel guilty.
And you're doing it to yourself. If
you're sick and tired of it, stop doing
it.
You don't deserve it.
You don't have to keep doing it. It's
something you learn, but you don't have
to keep doing it.
You can give it up.
You can break that because you're
choosing to do it. It's in your power to
do so.
Is that something that you would prefer?
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> Then
do that. There is no reason until you
give yourself a reason
to feel that way. To feel guilty about
being yourself.
You're the one inventing the reasons to
feel guilty.
If you don't prefer it, stop doing it.
If you don't stop doing it, we can only
assume that you're not yet sick and
tired of being sick and tired of it.
But when you're really sick and tired of
it, you'll stop. Because you'll realize
you're the one doing it.
>> Wow.
>> Do you understand?
>> Mhm.
>> Is this helping?
>> Yeah, a lot.
>> All right.
>> I would have never known that. Um
But now you do. Does that make you feel
a little bit lighter?
>> Yes.
>> To know that you're the one that's in
control of this?
>> Yeah.
>> And that you can stop
because you say that it's not something
you prefer anymore, and it's that
simple.
Do you understand that it can work that
way?
>> It seems so easy.
>> It is.
That's the great surprise. It is that
easy. It really is. That easy.
It's been easy for you to feel guilty,
hasn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> So, it's just as easy to feel joy and
deservability and love for yourself.
Just as easy.
As easy as it's been for you to feel
guilty.
You did that with no effort at all.
You can choose
what you wish to experience with no
effort at all.
Feeling guilty effortlessly.
Feeling guilty should prove to you
how effortless it can be to feel
something else.
Because there's nothing within creation
that says
that you have to feel one thing or
another. It's up to you.
And it shows you how effortless it is by
allowing you to experience what you
believe
you should be experiencing
effortlessly.
So, if you believe you should be feeling
guilt,
guilt is effortlessly there.
But, if you now realize that you don't
prefer to feel that anymore, then it
just becomes one of a number of choices
of things to experience.
And if you really say, "Well, you know
what? It was valid for the time because
it has brought me to a place where I
have learned that this is no longer what
I prefer. So, thank you, guilt,
for bringing me here.
And now, it's important to let you rest.
And I now choose to experience something
different just as effortlessly as I
experienced you."
How's that sound?
>> That sounds really good.
>> Yes, it does, doesn't it?
>> Yeah. So,
>> help you?
>> Yes, it does.
>> All right.
>> Um part of that also, if
So, if you're 100% [snorts]
yourself, there's no way
it can
What What how
>> When you are 100% yourself, there is no
way you can automatically experience
that which is not you.
You always, as 100% yourself, always
have the ability to choose to do so.
But, when you are 100% yourself, it
doesn't appear to make sense to give
yourself any other choice than being
you.
That's how you stay in that state. It
simply doesn't make sense to choose
anything other than being you.
There is no other choice.
But, you always have the ability to
choose.
But, everything just becomes an equally
valid choice. Negative, positive, hey,
it's an equally valid choice because it
can all be used in whatever way you
wish.
So, when you remove the stigma
from the choice, and everything is
equal,
well, then you can choose what you
prefer without invalidating what you
don't. It's just in the pool of choices.
That's all.
It's like saying, "Well, I'm going to go
into a candy store.
And there is this candy, and I don't
really fancy that so much, and there is
this candy, and I don't really fancy
that so much. Oh, look, there's my
favorite candy. I'm going to choose
that." Now, you understand that other
people might love the candy that you're
not that fancy about. So, it's just
another choice. It's not like you go,
"Oh, I'm going to be so guilty for
choosing my favorite candy because I've
left those other candies behind. Oh, no,
what will people think of me that I
didn't choose those?"
>> That's how I feel.
>> I know, but when I paint the picture
this way, doesn't it seem a little bit
silly?
>> Yeah.
>> So, that's the way you need to look at
what you're doing.
You need to paint a picture for yourself
that allows you to see how nonsensical
what you're choosing is.
Make sense?
>> Mhm.
>> And I don't mean it in a judgmental way.
I'm saying it is literally nonsensical
for who you actually are. It doesn't
make sense to choose something you're
not.
That's where all of your struggles come
from. All the pain you experience in
life is resistance to your true self.
That's what it is. It's resistance to
your true self. That's what creates the
sensation and the experience of pain.
Resistance.
Go with the flow.
It knows where to take you.
Yes?
>> Mhm.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes.
>> Then flow.
Thank you.
>> Thank